Right now we're going to show you the proper way to measure for a neck measurement on for your shirt.
Last thing you want is a tight shirt that's going to make you choke all night.
You're going to be uncomfortable already so we want you to be as comfortable as possible.
There are three basic shirt types: there are wing-tip collars and there's the lay down collar, mandarin collar.
Same thing is in common with all of them though; they all take the same type of measuring to determine the neck size.
So, you do that is you go right around the neck above the shirt -- there's actually about three way you can do this -- but pull it tight and then whatever measurement you get add an inch to that.
And that's how I do it most of the time.
But there's another way to do it is you can go around the neck.
Leave your fingers on the inside of the tape and pull it snug, but you're going to have a little bit of a gap because of the fingers in there.
You really want the shirt to be about an inch bigger than what your neck is so that you'll be comfortable.
The third option would be just to find a dress shirt in the closet that fits nice, usually in the back of the neck will have the size of the shirt and in those cases just write down whatever that shirt size is and that'll work fine.
So, three ways -- all of them should work fine if you take your time and do it right, but leave a little bit of a gap.